book2trip.com 2016-11-06

# Book2Trip

### **Privacy Policy**

**BOOK2TRIP**  believes in protecting your privacy. Please review our current Privacy Policy, which also governs your use of  **BOOK2TRIP** , to understand our practices.

TRUST. We understand that making purchases and travel plans online involves a great deal of trust on your part and we respect your privacy. We take this trust very seriously, and make it our highest priority to ensure the security and confidentiality of the personal information you provide to us. Please read the following policy to learn about our privacy practices. By visiting our website, [ **BOOK2TRIP.com**](http://www.book2trip.com/), you are accepting the practices described herein.

**What Personal Information We Collect**

**In General**

We receive and store any information you enter on our Website or give us in any other way. This includes information that can identify your ("personal information"), including your first and last name, telephone number, postal code, and e-mail addresses, and, in some cases, billing information. We also may request information about your traveler preferences. You can choose not to provide information to us, but in general some information about you is required in order for you to register as a member; purchase products or services; complete a traveler profile; participate in a survey, contest, or sweepstakes; ask us a question; or initiate other transactions on our website.

**Information from Other Sources**

**BOOK2TRIP  **does not currently use independent third-party sources to add to our user account information or delivery and address information.

**Automatic Information**

We automatically collect some information about your computer when you visit  **BOOK2TRIP**. For example, we will collect your IP address, Web browser software (such as Google Chrome or Internet Explorer), and referring Website. We also may collect information about your online activity, such as properties viewed, reservations sent, and purchases made. One of our goals in collecting this automatic information is to help customize your user experience.

**Cookies and Other Web Technologies**

When you visit  **BOOK2TRIP** , we may assign your computer a "cookie" (a small, unique identifier text file). For example, whenever you sign in as a  **BOOK2TRIP  **member, we record your member ID and the name on your member account in the cookie file on your computer. We also may record your password in this cookie file, if you checked the box entitled "Save this password for automatic sign-in." Note that member IDs, passwords, and any other account-related data included in such cookies are encrypted for security purposes. You can always choose not to receive a cookie file by enabling your Web browser to refuse cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie. Please note that if you refuse to accept cookies from  **BOOK2TRIP** , you may not be able to access many of the travel tools we offer.

**Information Collected by Third-Party Advertising Companies**

Third-party advertisers, such as those we use to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet, may use cookies and other technologies (such as Web beacons or single-pixel GIFS) for several purposes, including: to measure the effectiveness of their ads; to analyze, modify, and personalize advertising content on  **BOOK2TRIP  **and other sites; and to provide ads about goods and services we hope will be of interest to you. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

**How We Use Your Personal Information**

**BOOK2TRIP  **does not sell user information, including name, email address, contact information, phone number, or any other personally identifiable information, to third-parties.  **BOOK2TRIP**  uses information about you for the following general purposes: to provide you with the products and services you request; to provide you with travel confirmation and updates; to manage your account, including processing bills and providing travel notifications; to communicate with you in general; to respond to your questions and comments; to measure interest in and improve our products, services, and Website; to notify you about special offers and products or services that may be of interest to you; to otherwise customize your experience with  **BOOK2TRIP** ; to solicit information from you, including through surveys; to resolve disputes, or troubleshoot problems; to prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities; to enforce our General Terms of Use; and as otherwise described to you at the point of collection.

If you provide your email address to  **BOOK2TRIP** , you agree to allow us to add your email to our database of users. You may receive one or more promotional emails either from us or one our affiliates. You are welcome to opt not to receive these promotional messages. In the event that you use any of our tools that we may from time to time offer that integrate in any way with a third party website to which you have provided data or information, you acknowledge and agree that such third party website shall be responsible for how the data or information you have provided to such website is handled.

**BOOK2TRIP  **may share your information with the following entities:

Travelers, such as vacation rental Hosts/Owners. Throughout  **BOOK2TRIP** , we do not share your email address with these traveler s unless they need it to fulfill the travel reservation you have made on  **BOOK2TRIP** , and we restrict their use of this information to that purpose. We do not place limitations on our traveler s' use or disclosure of your other personal information. Therefore, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of any travel traveler whose products you purchase through  **BOOK2TRIP**. Please note that these traveler s also may contact you as necessary to obtain additional information about you or to facilitate your travel reservation.

Sharing this information with our affiliates, enables us to provide you with information about products and services, both travel-related and other, which might interest you. To the extent that our corporate affiliates have access to your information, they will follow practices that are at least as restrictive as the practices described in this Privacy Policy. They also will comply with applicable laws governing the transmission of promotional communications and, at a minimum, give you an opportunity in any commercial e-mail they send to choose not to receive such e-mail messages in the future.

We also may share your information: (i) in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law; (ii) to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of  **BOOK2TRIP** , our customers, or others; and in connection with our General Terms of Use and other agreements; and (iii) in connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

Other than as set out above, you will be notified when personal information about you will be shared with third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to have us share such information.

We also may share aggregate or anonymous information with third parties, including advertisers and investors. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of visitors a Website receives or what are the most popular vacation destinations. This information does not contain any personal information and is used to develop content and services we hope you will find of interest.

**How You Can Access Your Personal Information**

You can access your information at various points on  **BOOK2TRIP**  Website. These include: your  **BOOK2TRIP  **Profile page, where you can view, update, or change your personal information and update your member profile, travel preferences, and associated information; (ii) the Account page, where you can change your password.

**Your Choices Regarding Collection and Use of Your Information**

As discussed above, you can choose not to provide us with any information, although it may be needed to make travel reservations, contact our travelers, or take advantage of certain features offered on BOOK2TRIP.

You can also add or update information on your  **BOOK2TRIP  **Profile, and Account pages as described above.

The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Please note that if you refuse to accept cookies from  **BOOK2TRIP** , you will not be able to access portions of our Website.

**How We Protect Your Personal Information**

We want you to feel confident about using  **BOOK2TRIP  **to plan your vacation rental and purchase your travel, so we are committed to protecting the information we collect. While no Website can guarantee security, we have implemented appropriate administrative, technical, and physical security procedures to help protect the personal information you provide to us. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they only may do so for permitted business functions. In addition, we use encryption when transmitting your sensitive personal information between your system and ours, and we employ firewalls and intrusion detection systems to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your information.

**Children's Privacy**

**BOOK2TRIP  **does not sell travel or other services for purchase by children. Should a child whom we know to be under 13 send personal information to us, we will use that information only to respond directly to that child to inform him or her that we must have parental consent before receiving his or her personal information.

**External Links**

If any part of the  **BOOK2TRIP  **Website links you to other Websites, those Websites do not operate under this Privacy Policy. We recommend you examine the privacy statements posted on those other Websites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

**BOOK2TRIP  **may update this Privacy Policy in the future. We will notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the e-mail address you provided to us or by placing a prominent notice on our Website.

**How You Can Contact Us**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy (or your travel planning or purchases), please e-mail us at [support@Book2Trip.com](mailto:support@Book2Trip.com).

This Privacy Policy is effective as of April 1, 2016.

**Payment Protection Policy**

**Terms and Conditions**

We provide the Vacation Rentals Payment Protection Policy (the “Policy”) to Guests who agree to pay the Hosts through their agreement; any payment transaction is based on the sole connection between the Host and the Guest for rental properties.

The terms “you, “your” or “User” refer to the customer/guest who visit our website  **(**[ **Book2Trip.com**](http://www.book2trip.com/)) and connect with the Host using our  **BOOK2TRIP  **Platform to rent a rental property displayed on the Website (each, a “Rental”).  The Websites (and all associated domains).

If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of the Policy, then you have no right to obtain reimbursement or claim any other rights under the Policy.

We may revise this Policy at any time and in our sole discretion by amending the applicable web page on the Website or by publishing notices elsewhere on the Website.

  **Claim requirements**

To qualify for reimbursement under this Policy, you must ensure that:

  1. your claim falls within one or more of the Covered Circumstances (as defined below);
  2. you paid for the Rental to the Host/Owner;
  3. you took all reasonable steps to resolve the issue with the property owner/Host (the “Owner”);
  4. you are the person who made the booking; and
  5. you comply with all other requirements under the Policy.

The maximum amount in aggregate that we will reimburse you under this Policy (the “Coverage Limit”) is the lower of the total amount you paid through the Platform for the Rental (the “Qualifying Payment”).

**Circumstances covered under this Policy**

We will reimburse you for your losses up to the Coverage Limit, provided that you meet the claim requirements described above and one or more of the following “Covered Circumstances” applies:

  1. **Fraudulent Advertisement:  **the Owner does not own or manage the Rental, or is not the authorized agent of the property’s owner, or the Rental is not legally permitted to be rented.
  2. **Compromised Owner** : the personal e-mail address of the Owner or the Owner’s account with us has been compromised by a fraudulent individual purporting to be the true Owner to induce payment from you.
  3. **Inaccessible Rental** : you have paid for the Rental in compliance with the booking contract, and you have complied with the Owner’s terms and conditions but you have been denied entry to the Rental as a result of intentional and wrongful conduct of the Owner (which is deemed to include as a result of the Owner’s bankruptcy, insolvency or fraudulent activity), or the Rental is not in fact for rent. You will not be covered for any delay in accessing the Rental during the rental period. You must notify us of this condition no later than the first day of your expected rental period.
  4. **Misrepresented Rental** : the Rental has Material Differences or Defects (as defined below) compared with the advertised Rental, and: (i) you are unable to rent the Rental as intended; (ii) you document the Material Differences or Defects; and (iii) you notify the Owner and us of this condition no later than the first day of your rental period.

The meaning of “ **Material Differences or Defects** ” shall be determined in our sole discretion and, among other exceptions, it shall not cover cleanliness of the Rental; minor differences in the location of the Rental advertised and the actual location of the Rental; the presence or availability of local attractions; or maintenance issues with amenities or services.

**Circumstances not covered under this Policy**

We will not provide any reimbursement for loss of funds due to circumstances that are not included in the Covered Circumstances. For clarification, we will not cover losses in any of the following circumstances (which is not an exhaustive list).

  1. Any indirect losses; losses associated with travel arrangements, such as airfare or other transportation costs; opportunity losses; contractual losses; consequential losses; losses due to the weather or natural disasters; any losses other than the Qualifying Payment (subject to the Coverage Limit).
  2. If we or the Owner offer you alternative accommodation in lieu of the Rental and you accept the alternative accommodation (which will be inferred if you stay at least one night at such alternative accommodation), you will not be able to claim in respect of any sums paid for the original Rental.
  3. Any damage deposits or other funds paid to the Host/Owner using the Platform that are not returned due to damage or non-compliance with the Owner’s booking contract and/or cancellation policy.
  4. Any payments made in cash, or by cheque or wire transfer, or using any other type of payment service in agreement with the Host/Owner.
  5. If you have a close personal connection with the Owner, for example, you are friends or members of the same family.
  6. Payments you make after we notify you that the Rental is fraudulent or has been removed from the Website.
  7. In relation to a Rental with Material Differences or Defects, where you fail to notify us no later than the first day of your rental period and you do not vacate the Rental by midnight on the day of check-in.

**Claim Process**

To make a claim under the Policy, you must take the following steps within the time periods described below.

  1. Inform us of the problem no later than the first day of your rental period by sending an email to [ **SUPPORT@BOOK2TRIP.COM**](mailto:SUPPORT@BOOK2TRIP.COM).
  2. Send a completed [ **Claim form**](https://www.book2trip.com/contactus)  to us with proof of identification and a detailed description of the circumstances surrounding your claim so that we receive it within 14 days of the first day of your rental period.
  3. Submit the Claim Form by email to [ **SUPPORT@BOOK2TRIP.COM**](mailto:SUPPORT@BOOK2TRIP.COM). Alternatively, you can print the form and submit the form by post. (Please e-mail us to request the applicable address for submission).
  4. If the issue is due to fraudulent activity you must obtain a police crime reference number/ case number in relation to such issue and print it on the Claim Form. Details of how to obtain a crime reference number/ case number are included on the Claim Form.

We shall complete the reimbursement claim process in a reasonable time frame (generally within four weeks) and will keep you informed of any decisions or additional documentation required to process your claim.

In our sole discretion, we shall make all decisions regarding claim and documentation requirements and eligibility under the Policy. Our decisions shall be final and binding on you.

**Host Agreement**

**(a) Registration.  **By registering or signing into your account on this Website as a vacation rental owner or Host ("Host"), you agree to provide accurate and current information about yourself as prompted by the registration process and maintain and promptly update your online profile information to keep it accurate and current, including but not limited to the information displayed in your  **BOOK2TRIP  **account. By registering or signing into your account on this Website as a Host with a listed vacation rental property (a "Listing" and collectively "Listings") on this Website, You represent and warrant that (i) you own and control all of the rights to the content, including text, descriptions, photos and any other content that you post or otherwise distribute regarding the Listings, or you otherwise have the lawful right to post and distribute such content to or through the Website; (ii) such content is accurate and not misleading (including, without limitation, descriptions, features, availability and rental pricing, and pictures (whether supplied by you or authorized by you to be taken by  **BOOK2TRIP  **from another web site or service)); and (iii) use and posting or other transmission of such content does not violate this Agreement and will not violate any rights of or cause injury to any person or entity. You also agree to promptly provide proof of personal identification, ownership of the property listed or authority to list the property as we may request. We reserve the right to refuse, in our sole discretion, any Listing or remove Listings, either temporarily or permanently based on the content and accuracy of such Listing, including without limitation, accurate calendar availability and rate information. We may refuse to publish the Listing for any reason, and you hereby expressly agree to release and hold us harmless from any loss or liability that may arise from such a decision.

**(b) Term, Renewal, and Cancellation.**  As applicable to you, Listings are sold to run for entire term from the date of payment. Payment for subscriptions for Listings must be made in the valid currency of your country; paid either by major credit card or debit card. Such Listing subscriptions shall automatically renew at the expiration of the then-current term, monthly or annual as applicable, for an additional term of the same duration as the initial term. This automatic-renewal allows your service to remain uninterrupted. If you do not wish for your Listing subscription to be automatically renewed, you must manually cancel your Listing subscription by accessing your  **BOOK2TRIP  **account and cancelling prior to the expiration of the then-current term. Upon any cancellation, your Listing subscription will remain active through your then-current term; however your Listing subscription will not be automatically renewed upon the expiration of this term. If your subscription is cancelled at the end of your then-current Listing subscription term for any reason and you thereafter desire to renew your Listing subscription, you will be required to pay the then-current non-promotional subscription rate to activate a new subscription. If you do not cancel your Listing subscription you re-affirm and authorize us to charge your credit card at the end of each subscription term for an additional term of the same duration as the initial term and at the then-current non-promotional subscription rate. You agree to be responsible for any such charges, and we reserve the right to obtain payment directly from you if necessary. You may disable a Listing prior to the end of the term and thus remove the Listing from the Website, however, disabling a Listing will not cancel your subscription. No refunds or extensions of time are available for disabled or cancelled Listing subscriptions.

**(c) Complaints and Removal of Listings.**  If we become aware of or receive a complaint from any person or entity regarding a member's Listing or rental practices that, in our sole discretion, warrants the immediate removal of such member's allegedly offensive Listing from the Website (for example, and without limitation, if a member double-books a property for multiple travelers on the same date, or engages in any practice that, in our sole discretion, would be considered unfair within the vacation rental industry, or if we receive a complaint that any listing's content infringes on the rights of a third party or the user has been fraudulently posting reviews or violation of this Agreement), then we may immediately remove the allegedly offensive Listing from the Website without notice to the member and without refund while we investigate the basis for the complaint. If we conclude, in our sole discretion, that any such complaint is meritorious, then we may permanently remove the offensive Listing from the site without notice to the member and without refund.

**(d) Content Restrictions.**  You represent and warrant that each Listing displays an individual and uniquely identified property available for short term rent.  **BOOK2TRIP  **reserves the right to amend or remove any Listing, when more than one property is described or a Host may be listing only a subset of their total Listings and directing Guests to other rentals not included on the Website, and may choose, in its sole discretion to retain any fees associated with the non-conforming listing as compensation for violating this condition. You agree that each Listing is subject to review and  **BOOK2TRIP  **reserves the right to edit, amend, improve any Listing and the design, layout and functionality of Listings and the Website, in its sole discretion and without notice to you. You represent and warrant that the Listings will not contain addresses of other web sites, HTML, code or other markup languages, other than as provided herein. Addresses of other web sites, HTML, code, or other markup languages will be removed from Listings without notice. You agree not to place email addresses within your listings other than in the designated area to help prevent SPAM and discourage email harvesting robots from crawling BOOK2TRIP. Email addresses included outside designated areas will be removed from Listings without notice.

**(e) Content License.  **You grant BOOK2TRIP, its affiliates, and licensees (i) a nonexclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, transferable, irrevocable right to use, reproduce, modify, edit, adapt, translate, distribute, publish, create derivative works from and publicly display and perform such content throughout the world in any media, now known or hereafter devised; (ii) the right to use the name that you submit in connection with such content, if they choose; and (iii) you grant BOOK2TRIP and its affiliates the ability to copyright and protect the images, copy and other content available via your Listing from the unauthorized use by unaffiliated third parties who may attempt to use such information and grant us the right to pursue at law any person or entity that violates your or BOOK2TRIP's rights in the content by a breach of this Agreement. You further agree to assist us - at our expense and control - to protect such copyrighted material from unauthorized redistribution. We are not responsible for any infringement or violation of laws resulting from content supplied by any member and each member will indemnify and hold harmless BOOK2TRIP against any action brought for breach of copyright or other rights from the use of such content. You hereby waive and release all rights to any claim against us for any alleged or actual infringement of any proprietary rights, rights of privacy and publicity, moral rights and rights of attribution in connection with any user-contributed content posted or provided to us. You agree that we may reproduce in whole or in part any photographic material supplied by you in the promotion of your property or the promotion of the Website.

**(f) Other Rights in Content.**  You understand that content submitted will be considered non-confidential and BOOK2TRIP, its affiliates, and licensees will be under no obligation to treat such content as proprietary information. Without limiting the foregoing, **BOOK2TRIP** , its affiliates, and licensees reserve the right to use the content as they deem appropriate, including, without limitation, deleting, editing, modifying, rejecting, or refusing to post it. **BOOK2TRIP** , its affiliates, and licensees are under no obligation to offer you any payment for content that you submit or the opportunity to edit, delete or otherwise modify content once it has been submitted to  **BOOK2TRIP**.  **BOOK2TRIP** , its affiliates, and licensees shall have no duty to attribute authorship of content to you, and shall not be obligated to enforce any form of attribution by third parties.

**(g) Responsibilities as Host.**  You acknowledge that: (i) you will be responsible for and agree to abide by and adhere to all laws, rules and regulations applicable to the advertisement of your rental and the conduct of your rental business, including, but not limited to, permits, licenses, zoning regulations, occupancy taxes, zoning ordinances, safety compliance and compliance with all anti-discrimination and fair housing laws; (ii)  **BOOK2TRIP  **is not a property management company; (iii) prospective renters will contact you directly using the email contact, booking, or the contact information provided with the Listing; (iv)  **BOOK2TRIP  **is not responsible for renters of property (it is your responsibility to validate the qualifications of the prospective renters and rent a Listing on terms and conditions acceptable to you); and (v)  **BOOK2TRIP  **may, at no additional cost to you, license third-party web sites to advertise the Listings in order to maximize the visitors to your listing.

**(h) Disabling Listings.  **You understand that you may disable any Listing at any time (such listing will generally be removed from  **BOOK2TRIP**  within seven business days).

**(i) Prohibited Activities.  **You agree not to post, email, or approve for posting, content, whether in Listings or otherwise: that violates the Fair Housing Act by stating a discriminatory preference based on race, color, national origin, religion, sex, familial status or handicap, or violates any state or local law prohibiting discrimination on the basis of these or other characteristics; that is false, deceptive, misleading, deceitful, misinformative, or constitutes "bait and switch"; that infringes any patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright or other proprietary right of any third party, or that you do not have a right to make available under any law or contractual or fiduciary relationship; that contains software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment; or that employs misleading email addresses, or forged headers or otherwise manipulated identifiers in order to disguise the origin of content transmitted through the Website.

**(j) Accuracy of Listings.**  As a Host, you may provide or approve Listings. You represent and warrant that all information contained in Listings will be true and accurate in all material respects and will not omit anything that may be material to the decision of a user interested in a transaction. You understand that renters will rely upon your Listings and any misstatements or omissions about the Listing may result in liability and other consequences to you including but not limited to cancellation of your Listing and/or account with  **BOOK2TRIP**. You expressly release  **BOOK2TRIP  **and its users from any liabilities or obligations that may arise from any misrepresentations, omissions, or misstatements in the Listings you provide to  **BOOK2TRIP  **(including Listings you approve) and others who use the Website. You may also provide limited additional rules or rental policies and agreements of use for your Listings, but  **BOOK2TRIP**  will have no obligation to monitor, police or enforce such rules, and  **BOOK2TRIP  **will have no liability or obligation to you or to a renter for any violation of such rules. You understand and agree that  **BOOK2TRIP**  is a referral service only, and in no event shall  **BOOK2TRIP  **be a party to any rental contract or agreement between you and a Guest.

**(k) Contact Information.  **As a Host, you represent and warrant that contact information for past guests that you enter into the Website through our service or other automated processes (including providing contact information of past guests directly to  **BOOK2TRIP** ), shall be the valid contact information of past renters. If such contact information is provided in relation to a specific Listing, you represent and warrant that to the best of your knowledge such information is accurate and renters are truly and accurately associated with Listings that they rented.

**(l) Reviews.**  You hereby agree to allow  **BOOK2TRIP  **to send review requests on your behalf based on the contact information (email address) of past guests' that you provide and that  **BOOK2TRIP  **shall have the right to retain this contact information, including the guests' name and email address for record keeping purposes.  **BOOK2TRIP  **respects the privacy of your customers and our users and hereby agrees not to reuse this information for remarketing purposes. Users that register an account with  **BOOK2TRIP  **shall be subject to this Agreement and may be contacted in connection with  **BOOK2TRIP  **services or information.

**(m) Confirming or Rejecting Bookings.**  When a Host requests payment from a traveler, that quote is sent to that potential guest, who can confirm the booking by submitting payment to the Host/Owner himself. The quote will expire automatically once the date the Host schedules the first payment to be due is in the past or cancels the quote.

**(n) BOOK2TRIP as Limited Agent.**  As a Host, you are solely responsible for collecting your Listing Payments made by Guests on your behalf and agree that payments made by Guests shall be made directly to you. You agree to make the Listing available to the Guest as if you had received the Total Fee and will honor your cancellation policies. In connection with such appointment,  **BOOK2TRIP  **assumes no liability for any of your acts or omissions. Any Payment transactions are solely discussed between Hosts and Guests.

**(o) Collection and Remittance of Rental Fee.  **When using your presented payment methods as a Host, you will solely collect the Total Fee (defined above) from the Guest at the time the Guest accepts the Host's booking request, subject to any Scheduled Payments (detailed above) and will remit the Rental Fee to you either: (i) within 24 hours of processing the Guest's payment if you are approved for a merchant account through our third-party processor; or (ii) if you are not eligible for a merchant account, within 24 hours after the Guest checks in at the Listing.

**(p) Security Deposits.  **If a Security Deposit is included in a Listing for a confirmed booking,  **BOOK2TRIP  **will not obtain a pre-authorization of the Guest's credit card in the amount the Host determines for the Security Deposit in the booking request.  **BOOK2TRIP  **is not responsible for adjudicating and managing security deposit disputes and disclaims liability in this regard.

**(q) Payments for Hosts/Owners.**  In consideration for presenting Payment solutions for Hosts/Owners,  **BOOK2TRIP  **does not charge neither; (a) a fee to the Host based upon a percentage of the amount of the Rental Fee, excluding Taxes, nor (b) a fee to the Guest based upon a percentage of the amount of the Rental Fee excluding Taxes as disclosed to the Guest prior to his or her confirmation of payment for the Listing.  **BOOK2TRIP  **is only a marketing tool, which helps Hosts and Guests connect for booking vacation rentals.

**(r) Cancellations and Refunds.**  If you cancel a quote via our Website, we will notify the Guest that the Listing is no longer available. If you cancel a confirmed booking made via our Website, the cancellation policy for the Listing will apply to and govern the terms of your cancellation and amount, if any, of the Total Fee to be refunded to the Guest. Hosts may not process any necessary refunds through their  **BOOK2TRIP  **account, including full or partial refunds for Security Deposits collected, at any time between the date the Guest confirms their reservation and within thirty days following the Guest check-out date.  **BOOK2TRIP  **is not responsible for refunding the Total Fee for such booking to the applicable Guest within a commercially reasonable time of the cancellation or refund. After such thirty-day period, any refunds to the Guest must be done external to the Website.  **BOOK2TRIP  **is not part of this transaction.

**(s) Host Cancellation Fee.**  If you cancel a confirmed booking for any reason, a HOST may impose a fee (the “Cancellation Fee”), which he will either charge to you directly or withhold from your future disbursements, in your sole discretion. This is because cancellations can have serious implications on a traveler’s trip, and cause you to incur costs. You will be notified of the situations in which a Cancellation Fee applies before you decide to cancel. You accept that the Cancellation Fee represents a genuine pre-estimate of our loss which is necessarily incurred in dealing with travelers’ complaints resulting from your cancellation, and the sourcing and securing of appropriate alternative accommodation on their behalf. For the avoidance of doubt, once you accept a booking, you are under an obligation to fulfill it. If you breach this obligation and cancel a booking, then the Host/Owner may impose the Cancellation Fee.

The Cancellation Fee will generally be charged in the same currency in which the cancelled booking was denominated. 

Prospective travelers will be able to see the number of cancellations you have initiated, as this figure will be displayed next to your Listing. A higher than average rate of cancellation is likely to reduce the number of bookings you receive, and if we conclude, in our sole discretion, that your cancellation rate is excessive, then we may permanently remove your Listing from the site without notice to the Host. 

**  (t) BOOK2TRIP Liability.** We act for you in a limited capacity as a marketplace, for the purpose of providing a marketing tool for travelers to book and rent a property. However, we are not party to your rental transactions with Guests and are not responsible for ensuring that Guests make the payments due in relation to their bookings. We also are not responsible for chargebacks, cancellations, refunds, or any disputes between you and Guests. You shall not hold  **BOOK2TRIP  **responsible for any acts or omissions of Guests.

Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.

**SERVICE HELP**

For answers to frequently asked questions, please [ **Contact Us**](http://www.book2trip.com/contactus) or send us an email to [ **support@book2trip.com**](mailto:support@book2trip.com) for additional questions, comments of service help.

Last updated: April 25, 2016
